ILR School Office of Career Services "Union Days" Posters /4319 G
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Office of Career Services "Union Days" Posters
1999-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Office of Career Services
/4319 G
6.11 cubic feet
4.7 linear ft.
Graphic document genres.
ILR School 'Union Day' Posters
8828237
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 06, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4274: ILR School Event Publicity
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Office of Career Services; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8828237
- Union Days 2012 poster (framed) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Workers Without Borders Poster, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Union Days 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Days 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Union Days 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Union Days 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Union Days 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Union Days 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Union Days 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Union Days 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Union Days 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Union Days 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Union Days 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Union Days 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)